Welcome to the Jam!
Space Jam: A New Legacy is a family, comedy,
adventure film directed by Malcolm D. Lee.
When LeBron and his young son Dom are trapped in a digital space by a rogue A.I., LeBron must get them home safe by leading Bugs, Lola Bunny
and the whole gang of notoriously undisciplined Looney Tunes to victory over the A.I.'s digitized champions on the court.
It's Tunes versus Goons in the highest-stakes challenge of his life.
LeBron James, played by LeBron James.
Al G. Rhythm, played by Don Cheadle.
Dominic 'Dom' James, played by Cedric Joe.
Bugs Bunny / Sylvester / Yosemite Sam / Fred
Flintstone (voice), played by Jeff Bergman.
Speedy Gonzales (voice), played by Gabriel Iglesias.
Lola Bunny (voice), played by Zendaya.
Space Jam: A New Legacy is a 2021 American
live-action/animated sports comedy film, directed by Malcolm D.
A sequel to Space Jam (1996), the film stars basketball player LeBron James as a fictionalized version of himself, in addition to featuring Don Cheadle,
Khris Davis and Sonequa Martin-Green in live-action roles, while Zendaya, Jeff Bergman and Eric Bauza headline the Looney Tunes voice cast.
The film follows James enlisting the Looney Tunes' aid to win a basketball game in a Warner Bros.–themed virtual
world against its rogue artificial intelligence ruler after his youngest son is abducted by the AI.
Discussions for a Space Jam sequel began following its release.
Director Joe Pytka was attached to return, and Spike Brandt and Tony Cervone signed on as the animation
directors; however, the project stalled due to lead actor Michael Jordan's refusal to return.
Several possible spin-offs focusing on other athletes, including Jeff Gordon,
Tiger Woods and Tony Hawk, were discussed but never materialized.
After several years in development, a LeBron James-led sequel was announced in 2014 with
filming under director Terence Nance beginning in the Los Angeles area in June 2019.
Nance left the project in July due to creative differences and was
replaced by Lee, with filming completed by September.
Traditional animation was done by Company 3 and Tonic DNA, while visual effects
and computer animation were outsourced to Industrial Light & Magic.
Space Jam: A New Legacy premiered in Los Angeles on July 12, 2021, and was
released nationwide in the United States by Warner Bros.
Pictures on July 16, and through HBO Max for one month.
The film was a commercial disappointment, grossing $164 million against a $150 million budget, and received generally negative
reviews from critics for its lack of humor, excessive runtime, and extensive product placement of WarnerMedia properties.
It won three of its four Golden Raspberry Award
nominations, including Worst Actor for James.
The film explores themes of sports, cartoon,
basketball, game, live action and animation.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.